IRYNA NFPRANOVA

i.nepranova@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/iryna-nepranova

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

A responsible, enthusiastic, reliable person with great experience working in a bank. I'm interested in Front-End development and everything related to it. In a short time, I have developed a deep understanding of web-based processes. I consider myself a fast learner with a great passion for new knowledge and technology. I would like to become a valuable member of your team.

Key Skills, Software & Apps:

JavaScript - HTML - CSS - SCCS - Bootstrap - React - Git - Figma

EDUCATION

Master of International Economics, East Ukrainian National University named after Volodymyr Dahl, Luhansk, Ukraine | 2013

Continuing Education:

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate, Coursera | 2023

Front-End Pro, Computer School Hillel, Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2022

Front-End Basic, Computer School Hillel, Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2019

The Fundamentals of Software Testing, QA TestLab Training Center, online, Ukraine | 2018

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

EXPERT, JSC "OTP Bank", Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2018-2019

- Selling bank products: credit cards, loans, premium debit cards, insurance
- Consulting concerning the bank's products current or future clients
- Researching and verifying account information and resolving problems for customers as necessary
- Achievement of individual goals and contribution to overall branch goals achievement

PERSONAL FINANCIAL CONSULTANT, JSC "Ukrsibbank", Kharkiv, Ukraine | 2016-2018

Selling bank products: credit cards, loans, premium debit cards, insurance

- Consulting concerning the bank's products current or future clients
- Researching and verifying account information and resolving problems for customers as necessary
- Achievement of individual goals and contribution to overall branch goals achievement

SENIOR INSPECTOR, The state department of revenue services in Luhansk City, Luhansk, Ukraine | 2013-2015

- Advising clients on financial matters
- Preparing and filing tax documents
- Creating reports

SOFT SKILLS

- Fast learner
- Adaptability
- Collaboration
- Result-oriented
- Time management

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Ukrainian: NativeRussian: Fluent

My projects at Github:

https://iryna-nepranova.github.io/portfolio/

https://github.com/lryna-Nepranova